let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: " Among 5 objects P, Q, R, S and T  i. R is twice as heavy as T  ii. S is one and half times as heavy as Q iii. Q and R together weigh as much as S and T together iv. P and S together are one and half time as heavy as Q and T together .Which among the five is the heaviest of all?",
    answer: "S",
    options: [
      "Q",
      "S",
      "P",
      "R"
    ]
  },
  {
  numb: 2,
    question: "There are five rods K, L, M, N and O. The weight of O is twice L. The weight of L is equal to the weights of K and M together. The weight of M is twice the weight of K. The weight of N is three times the weight of M. If the weight of N is 90 kg, what will be the weight of O? ",
    answer: "9θ kg",
    options: [
      "12θ kg",
      "6θ kg",
      "1θ5 kg",
      "9θ kg"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
      question: " Which is the odd term in the following series? CMQ, FPT, JTX, OYC, UFI ",
      answer: "UFI",
      options: [
        "FPT",
        "OYC",
        "JTX",
        "UFI"
      ]
    },
    {
     numb: 4,
        question: "Nehal, Iqbal, Ronit, Malini and Harbhajan participate in any one of the five activities i.e Quiz, Singing, Dance, Debate and Mimicry. Ronit participates in Singing. Harbhajan does not participate in Debate and Mimicry. Malini does not participate in Mimicry. Iqbal participates in Quiz. Who participates in Debate? ",
        answer: "Malini",
        options: [
        "Malini",
        "Nehal or Malini",
        "Nehal",
        "Cannot be determined"
      ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
           question: " In a row, seven people are standing for march past. I. B is standing right to A and left to C. II. D is standing left to E but right to C.  III. F is standing right to E and left to G.  Who is standing in the middle of the row?",
           answer: "D",
           options: [
           "D",
           "Either B or G",
           "A",
           "Either C or E"
         ]
       },
       {
        numb: 6,
           question: "The number in the Venn diagram indicates the number of persons/ people watching TV programmes. The diagram is drawn after surveying 150 persons in a population of 12,000. How many persons/ people can be expected to watch at least two TV programmes?",
           answer: "4320",
           options: [
           "4320",
           "3200",
           "5232",
           "5400"
         ]
       },
       {
        numb: 7,
           question: "The number in the Venn diagram indicates the number of persons/ people watching TV programmes. The diagram is drawn after surveying 150 persons in a population of 12,000. How many persons/ people can be expected to watch News only? ",
           answer: "2880",
           options: [
           "2280",
           "3200",
           "4320",
           "2880"
         ]
       },
       {
        numb: 8,
           question: " Which is the wrong term in the following series? pbd, reh, thl, vlp, xnt",
           answer: "vlp",
           options: [
           "xnt",
           "pbd",
           "thl",
           "vlp"
         ]
       },
       {
        numb: 9,
           question: "In a certain code, P @ R means P is the grandson of R; P $ R means P is the brother of R; P # R means P is the mother of R. If A @ B # C $ D, then how is B related to D?",
           answer: "Mother",
           options: [
           "Mother",
           "Husband",
           "Son",
           "Sister"
         ]
       },
       {
        numb: 10,
           question: "Choose a pair similar to the following. MDXF: OBZD",
           answer: "SGFN : UEHL",
           options: [
           "ILPR:KNRT",
           "SGFN:UEHL",
           "CLPQ:MXCF",
           "BMXT:COZW"
         ]
       },
];